Pastor's Study Conference records, 1980-2000.
Congregational Library & Archives
Pastor's Study Conference records, 1980-2000.
RG5055
Congregational Library & Archives
.53 Cubic Feet
(2 cases)
This pastor's group was comprised of United Church of Christ members from the New England and New York regions who met annually to discuss and study a theme or topic. Contains publicity brochures and, minutes, and working files for the yearly study conference spanning from 1980 through 2000.
Pastor's Study Conference (Springfield, Mass.)
Restrictions on Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted and open to the public. This collection has been minimally processed for access. Please contact the archivist or librarian for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Given as a gift by George E. Peters on June 14, 2013. Accession number 2013-05.
Biographical / Historical
From the context of the files, the purpose of the organization was to meet once a year at Springfield, Massachusetts, Old First Church, in February to discuss a theme selected by the planning committee. The members were within the United Church of Christ from New England and New York. The group has disbanded.
Scope and Contents
Contains publicity brochures and, minutes, and working files for the yearly study conference spanning from 1980 through 2000.
Arrangement
This collection maintains the original order in which the records were given to the library.
Associations, institutions, etc.
- Publicity, Brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Working File, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Working File, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Working File, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Working File, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Working File, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Working File, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Working File, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Working File, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Working File, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Working File, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)